[
    {
        "question": "how to do comment in css?",
        "answers": {
            "a": "/* This is a single-line comment */",
            "b": "/ This is a single-line comment /*",
            "c": "<-- This is a single-line comment -->",
            "d": "--< This is a single-line comment >--"
        },
        "correctAnswer": "a"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following allows specifying styles for the visual elements of the website ?",
        "answers": {
            "a": "Cascading Style sheets",
            "b": "Web page",
            "c": "Form",
            "d": "Animation"
        },
        "correctAnswer": "a"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is known as special symbol in the syntax of CSS ?",
        "answers": {
            "a": "Selector",
            "b": "Declaration",
            "c": "Rules",
            "d": "Input"
        },
        "correctAnswer": "c"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following are two main parts of CSS rule ?",
        "answers": {
            "a": "Select, declaration",
            "b": "Selector, declare",
            "c": "Selection, declaration",
            "d": "Selector, declaration"
        },
        "correctAnswer": "b"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is an HTML element on which style can be applied ?",
        "answers": {
            "a": "Declaration",
            "b": "Selector",
            "c": "Select",
            "d": "Declare"
        },
        "correctAnswer": "c"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is the syntax of CSS ?",
        "answers": {
            "a": "elect {property : value}",
            "b": "Selector {value : property}",
            "c": "Selector {property : value}",
            "d": "Selection {property : value}"
        },
        "correctAnswer": "c"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is a scripting language that allows adding programming to web pages ?",
        "answers": {
            "a": "Action script",
            "b": "JavaScript",
            "c": "HTML",
            "d": "CSS"
        },
        "correctAnswer": "b"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following is a scripting language that is simple, lightweight programming language that does not contain advanced programming functionalities ?",
        "answers": {
            "a": "JavaScript",
            "b": "HTML",
            "c": "C",
            "d": "Java"
        },
        "correctAnswer": "a"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which one of these is a JavaScript package manager?",
        "answers": {
            "a": "Node.js",
            "b": "TypeScript",
            "c": "npm",
            "d": "asp.net"
        },
        "correctAnswer": "c"
    },
    {
        "question": "Which of the following symbol signifies the start and end of a JavaScript block ?",
        "answers": {
            "a": "Semicolon",
            "b": "Square bracket",
            "c": "Curly bracket",
            "d": "Round bracket"
        },
        "correctAnswer": "c"
    }
]